[{"answer": "Because this is not a normal time.", "docId": "120925pmt", "aSentId": 18, "question": "How has he managed to avoid public retribution for not fixing the economy better than he has done?", "qSentId": 17}, {"answer": "I think the smart thing for us to do is to maintain constant conflict with the Israeli intelligence services and the Arab intelligence services who also don't want Iran to have a nuclear weapon.", "docId": "120925pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "What is the smart thing for America to do right now, given the ratcheting up of all the rhetoric on both sides?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "-- is they don't have a tenable position.", "docId": "120925pmt", "aSentId": 68, "question": "Do you trust him?", "qSentId": 67}, {"answer": "Not on this, I don't.", "docId": "120925pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "Do you trust Ahmadinejad?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "I shouldn't answer that question because of my wife's position and that's the president and the security team's desire to -- a decision to make.", "docId": "120925pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "If Israel was to launch an airstrike against Iran, a preemptive strike, because they believe, as appears to be the case with many of their top leadership, that Iran is right on the cusp now of developing a nuclear weapon -- if they do that, what should America's response be?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "First of all, it's very different from Iraq.", "docId": "120925pmt", "aSentId": 95, "question": "Can America -- can the world risk another flawed military action, if it turns out that Ahmadinejad is actually telling the truth?", "qSentId": 94}, {"answer": "Well, I think you know the debates are very important for him.", "docId": "120925pmt", "aSentId": 122, "question": "What words would you have for Mitt Romney, given the state of the election campaign right now?", "qSentId": 121}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "120925pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "Crucial?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "That's not the issue to me.", "docId": "120925pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "Is he -- is he principled, do you think, Mitt Romney?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "Because this is not a normal time.", "docId": "120925pmt", "aSentId": 159, "question": "How has he managed to avoid public retribution for not fixing the economy better than he has done?", "qSentId": 158}, {"answer": "Well, that's the -- what Speaker Gingrich said is true, but it's not the whole truth, that is we had one year when virtually nothing got done.", "docId": "120925pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "And what advice to give to Barack Obama to try and get into that kind of mindset with the Republicans?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "What I tried to do, when I started -- I said I'm going to give it 10 years and see where we are, if we can last 10 years.", "docId": "120925pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "What is the big achievement?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "Well, we had it for a good reason.", "docId": "120925pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "Why couldn't Bill Clinton just run again and be president for the next 30 years?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "LINTON: They -- there are only two countries I'm eligible to run for the leadership position is if I move to Ireland and buy a house, I can -- I can run for president of Ireland, because of my Irish heritage.", "docId": "120925pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "Are you available if it comes to -- I get this through?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "Well, this clearly will be one of the most compelling issues that the next president faces, either Obama in a second term or Romney in a first term.", "docId": "120925pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "What do we do about Iran and President Ahmadinejad?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, Piers, the evidence is not just intelligence services, but also the International Atomic Energy Agency that's had inspectors in there, though Tehran has interrupted and obstructed their inspections from time to time.", "docId": "120925pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "Can the west afford to go into any kind of military conflict with Iran, with Ahmadinejad, and then discover actually all he was saying turned out to be true?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, that's the dilemma in terms of turning to military action that may well be necessary at some point.", "docId": "120925pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "What do you do?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "Well, I would like to make a couple points, Piers.", "docId": "120925pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "What would a Romney administration do if Israel decides to go it alone?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "Well, he talked to Prime Minister Netanyahu the other day.", "docId": "120925pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "I say it again, P.J. Crowley, with the benefit of hindsight and the way this has all played out, wouldn't it have been more prudent for the president to have found time in his busy television schedule to do some meetings?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "Yes, for you, Richard Williamson.", "docId": "120925pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "Is that for me, Piers?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "First, I played college football.", "docId": "120925pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "What is your view of the touchdown, or the Fail Mary pass, as it's now being known?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "LINTON: Well, on the football game, no, I did not think it was a touchdown.", "docId": "120925pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "And as a European, do you fancy a bet?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "You got a deal.", "docId": "120925pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "Hundred dollars to a charity of our choice?", "qSentId": 465}]